## FrancescoMoca



# **about me**Italian 26 years old

#### contact

francescomoca.ml me@francescomoca.ml

+39 338 6463491

Via Gigliarelli 86, Perugia, Italy

### languages

Italian English

### programming languages

Javascript Solidity Python Java PHP Bash

#### web development

HTML5 CSS3 WebRTC SQL React Redux React Native Angularis Ionic

#### misc Linux

Git PyTorch OrientDB Latex

#### **summary**

My main interest is to use technologies such as the blockchain for the development of decentralized applications, both for the front end and the smart contract part.

I develop web applications, mainly using React as a framework, and hybrid mobile applications, although I also have some limited experience in native android development.

#### **experience**

2019-Now **BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER** 

Freelancer

I'm collaborating with Genuino World, a growing startup that deals with verification of authenticity of purchases, such as jerseys worn by football players.

In particular, I worked on the development of the blockchain part of their product:

- I developed a custom ERC721 smart contract together with a dashboard to create and manage NFT tokens.
- I'm currently working on a mobile wallet, developed using React Native, to allow users to interact with the tokens and exchange them.

2016-Now MOBILE DEVELOPER

Freelancer

I developed a mobile companion application for a board game, 3 Secrets, commissioned by DaVinci Editrice.

The game was released in 2017 and in the following years I continued to maintain the app, developed using the the Ionic framework (v1), to add new languages and features.

#### **education**

2016–2019 **M.Sc.** in Software techniques [110/110 with honors]

Università di Bologna

**Thesis:** "State channel on blockchain technologies: a case study on multiuser games" Peer to peer web application using layer 2 scaling solutions such as state channels to facilitate the implementation of blockchain-based games.

2015 **Erasmus+ Program** 

Adam Mickiewicz University (Poznań, PL)

I took part in the "Google Online Marketing Challenge", gaining experience with Adwords and online marketing.

2012-2016 **B.Eng.** in Computer Science [105/110]

**Thesis:** "Blockchain: Big Data Management"

Università degli Studi di Perugia

Web application useful to analyse the Bitcoin transaction flow through the use of oriented graphs to visualize the sequence of transactions contained in the blockchain.

#### other qualifications

2019 Ethereum Developer Program Online Bootcamp 2019

Consensys Academy

#### interests

**professional:** Blockchain, Cryptocurrencies, Decentralized Applications, Distributed Ledger Technologies, Machine Learning, Data Mining, Open Source, Linux, Usability and User Experience. **personal:** Travelling, Photography, Cooking, Rap Music, Videogames and Board Games.